{
    "subject": "resource/Costanzo_Preve",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Piedmont",
    "human_readable": "Costanzo Preve was born in Piedmont.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8934293389320374,
            "question": "Where was Costanzo Preve born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6213110685348511,
            "question": "What is Costanzo Preve known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3336063027381897,
            "question": "Can you name any famous people born in Piedmont?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24073860049247742,
            "question": "What country is Piedmont located in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21108025312423706,
            "question": "What is the culture like in Piedmont?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19723185896873474,
            "question": "Are there any historical events associated with Piedmont?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17935918271541595,
            "question": "What are some interesting facts about Piedmont?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17260442674160004,
            "question": "Is Piedmont a city or a region?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15336012840270996,
            "question": "What are some popular tourist destinations in Piedmont?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15078648924827576,
            "question": "What type of landscape does Piedmont have?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Costanzo Preve was born in Piedmont.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7763_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular tourist destinations in Piedmont?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7763_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Piedmont a city or a region?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7763_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some interesting facts about Piedmont?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7763_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7763_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7763_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7763_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7763_140.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7763_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7763_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7763_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7763_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7763_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7763_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the documents contain information about Costanzo Preve's birthplace, but it is not specifically stated as Piedmont. According to file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7763/re-ranker-msmarco/21.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7763/re-ranker-msmarco/101.txt, Costanzo Preve was born in Valenza, Piedmont, Italy. However, this does not necessarily mean that he was born in Piedmont specifically (as opposed to being born in a town or city within the region of Piedmont)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents states that Costanzo Preve was born on April 14, 1943, in Valenza, Piedmont, Italy. Therefore, it is correct to say that Costanzo Preve was born in Piedmont."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The birth geographical coordinates of Costanzo Preve are given as 45\u00b0 0\u2019 45\u201d North latitude and 8\u00b0 38\u2019 38\u201d East longitude, which corresponds to Piedmont, Italy. However, this information suggests that his birth location was in a specific region with these exact coordinates, rather than simply stating that he was born in Piedmont, implying that the statement \"Costanzo Preve was born in Piedmont\" might be too vague or general compared to the more precise geographical data provided.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}